
	let one = {
		question: "20% of immigrants are reported to be White.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "False",
		info: "There are more than 20%; 46% of immigrants reported their race as single-race White, 27% as Asian, 10% as Black, and 15% as some other race. About 2% reported having two or more races",
	};
	let two = {
		question: "DACA provides a pathway to citizenship.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "False",
		info: 'DACA does not provide a path to citizenship for recipients. Itâ€™s very difficult for DACA recipients to become citizens since most are not eligible for a green card. In order to become a citizen, one must first have a green card for 5 years. The primary way to get a green card is through "Family Reunification," which means an immediate relative or spouse who is a citizen must sponsor you and most people with DACA do not have that.',
  };
	let three = {
		question: "The wall is being built on the US-Mexico border",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "True",
		info: "Part of the wall is being built over O'odham land in Arizona and desecrating sacred sites.",
  };
	let four ={
		question: "The US grants asylum to more refugees than any other country.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "False",
		info: "From 1982 - 2017, the United States led the world in admitting refugees. However, Trump lowered the refugee ceiling down to 45,000 in 2017, but only admitted 22,500. For comparison,from January 2017 to September 2019 admitted 76,200. In 2016 alone, 85,500 refugees were admitted into the United States",
  };
	let five = {
		question: "We should prioritize citizenship to immigrants who can contribute to the economy.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "False",
		info: "Nope nope my bro: let's not base human life on their economic worth. This would be implying that people are only worth as much as the capital they can generate.",
  };
	let six = {
		question: "President Obama deported more immigrants than any other president to date",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "True",
		info: "Although the jury is still out for Trump, Obama deported somewhere around 2.8 &mdash; 3.4 million people during his presidency. Although there is conflicting information on the DHS and ICE websites, in their first three years of presidency, Obama deported about 400,000 more than Trump.",
  };
	let seven = {
		question: "More immigrants fall below the official poverty threshold than US citizens.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "True",
		info: "15% percent of immigrants were poor (as defined, family incomes below the official poverty threshold), compared to 13% of the U.S.-born population.",
  };
	let eight = {
		question: "ICE and DHS have been around for a long time.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "False",
		info: "The Department of Homeland Security was signed into law by President George W. Bush on November 25, 2002. ICE was established in March of 2003. Although the United States has a history of xenophobia, we need to stop normalizing the establishment of these new institutions, along with the long-standing ones."
  };
	let nine = {
		question: "3,780 people in ICE custody have contracted COVID-19.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "True",
		info: "As of July 28, 2020, ICE is reporting 3,835 cases of COVID-19 in facilities holding immigrants around the country.",
  };
	let ten = {
		question: "There are more Hispanics and Latinos in the US that are immigrants than nativeborns.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "False",
		info: "Many of the U.S. Hispanics are native born. Of the 59.8 million people in 2018 who self-identified as Hispanic or Latino, 33 percent (19.8 million) were immigrants and 67 percent (40 million) were native born.",
  };
	let eleven = {
		question: "It's easy to gain citizenship the right way.",
		answers: ["True", "False"],
		correctAnswer: "False",
		info: "To become a citizen, immigrants must first become a permanent resident (AKA green card holder) which is already very hard to get and can take a lot of time. After living in the US for five consecutive years, a green card holder may then apply for naturalization, which is the process of becoming a citizen. They must be 18 or older, able to read, write, and speak basic English, understand the US constitution, have knowledge of the US history and government, and take the oath of allegiance to the US. The naturalizatioin fee is $725, and the process can last 6-14 months. They must then complete an interview and test. The overall process is very very long and costly.",
	};
	let twelve = {
		question: 'Thank you for taking the quiz! Check out our "Additonal Resources" page for more info and ways to support immigrants.',
		answers: ["Yes", "Yes"],
		correctAnswer: ["Yes"],
		info: "Please contact us if you have any further questions!",

	};
let questions = [one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve];
